{
    "subject": "resource/I_Am_Curious_(Blue)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:1968_films",
    "human_readable": "I Am Curious (Blue) is about 1968 films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7184678316116333,
            "question": "What year were films about I Am Curious (Blue) released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7135050892829895,
            "question": "Is the movie I Am Curious (Blue) a documentary or a fictional film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6369138956069946,
            "question": "Was I Am Curious (Blue) a commercially successful film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6237937808036804,
            "question": "What genre of films are associated with I Am Curious (Blue)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6055278778076172,
            "question": "What impact did I Am Curious (Blue) have on cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5510971546173096,
            "question": "Who directed the film I Am Curious (Blue)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42013975977897644,
            "question": "What were some of the major themes explored in I Am Curious (Blue)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4194529354572296,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors or actresses in the film I Am Curious (Blue)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37399888038635254,
            "question": "Did I Am Curious (Blue) receive any critical acclaim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37074971199035645,
            "question": "Were there any sequels or spin-offs from I Am Curious (Blue)?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=I Am Curious (Blue) is about 1968 films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6960_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did I Am Curious (Blue) receive any critical acclaim?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6960_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors or actresses in the film I Am Curious (Blue)?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6960_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of the major themes explored in I Am Curious (Blue)?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6960_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6960_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6960_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6960_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6960_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6960_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6960_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6960_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6960_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6960_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6960_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like me to analyze more triples!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"I Am Curious (Blue) is about 1968 films.\" The documents mention \"How the Film Speaks to 1968\" and discuss the themes and context of both \"I Am Curious (Yellow)\" and \"I Am Curious (Blue),\" indicating their relevance to the cultural and social issues of 1968."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}